[Music]
[Applause]
there was a girl
at she said she cared about
me she tried to make my
world the way she thought it should
be all right ladies and gentlemen today
we are here to buy potentially a new car
now as you guys can see we have a
different type of service going on here
today we're getting picked up in a
go-kart because we're looking to buy a
speed tail so right now I have my
Bugatti I have the Porsche McLaren rolls
Roy I have like 10 cars but I don't have
a McLaren speed tail so we're getting
dropped off right now to see what it's
all about to see if it's worth $3
million and if we should even add it to
the fleet right now you know it's crazy
that like 2 years ago I had this and I
was super excited about it her
now I see a Huracan and I feel like it's
pathetic all right boys so I feel like
we were just here like 2 months ago
buying the GT3 RS but by the way I love
and we have some crazy content with that
coming very soon and I feel like I have
to do a car tour video I feel like I
have 15 cars new cars since the last car
video that I did and I got to do a new
one so let me know down in the comments
below if I should do it think with the
Bugatti alone you already yeah like
literally my last car collection was
about 2.3 million or something like that
now only one of my cars engulfs my whole
entire car collection from about a year
ago and we might add a speed tail to the
collection right now oh [__] bro I
forgot we always get 10 grand you get
everything done before like this is
fully done we'll give you the extra
10,000 that we made on the trade I had I
had paused it
okay whatever we'll figure it out here
in the deal if you guys don't know what
a McLaren speed s is I didn't know it's
about 2 hours ago I did my research on
the way here and this car is basically
rare as [__] and this should be like a
P1 should be one of these cars that
continue to go up in B like this right
here this is P1 and this right here is
the McLaren
speed if I tell this [__] to pull she
going my doggy don't smoke on [__]
unless it's UNL yeah this is sick I
don't really like the interior I'm not
going to lie it's pretty basic this kind
of like an old man yeah it looks like an
old man's spec could be length so bro
this is long credit is do what credits
do bro right right are you sure it's
even that fast how do you even open the
door oh look who's here look who's here
what a combination you like the hot
sauce huh those legs bro that's the guy
that own what is this I think that's the
door
handle no bro there's a camera in there
clearly dude holy [__] this [__] has no
mirrors wow how do you how do you [__]
do you open this I feel like one of
these girls that they be taking out on
dates and they pull it to the door and
they're like um how do I open the door
Hello Alex how are you 10K and soul
richer 10K and soul better I know we
have a an explanation for that we
apologize for that you know we we're in
a bit of a rush that day my neck
actually hurts a little
bit so I was
[Music]
like I apologize I'm here to make up for
that because there's a potential deal
line up with the speed TI well that
brings me on to the next thing there's a
reason we left it call for price yeah
show me show me right all right so what
the [__] is this bro speed tail baby
yeah check that
out all
right edit
that all right there she goes yeah oh
cuz it opens my how the [__] what's the
proper way on how to get ins silence so
I'm sure that there's many different
ways however that would not be the way
that I got it there cu you can't even
get out damn bro but whoever sits here
is like hella no you're good so this
vehicle will do 186 mph in about 12 1/2
13 seconds it'll do 250 mph for a top
speed 250 mph making it the fastest
McLaren today it's it's a serious son of
a gun I'd like to say that it has the
same engine from an Elva or 765 or any
of those the 4 L twin turbo V8 but it
does have a battery that helps it out uh
with all of the Power
[Music]
yep they only made 106 of these this is
car 69 no jokes okay that's sweetens of
the deal you know you have no side view
mirrors this car wasn't 100% street
legal in the US because of that however
just like the amg1 and any other Super
Hyper car that they only make it with
just cameras itself there are some sort
of gray areas that you can go ahead and
drive your car no problem you just can't
put 30,000 mi in a year cuz that means
you were dailying with it so Mclaren has
a series what they call longtail series
and this is definitely I think you know
the king of that series it is the
longest car that I've have seen I'm
pretty sure I'm 63 if I lay down flat
next to this thing I'm pretty sure I
don't even cover this rear end it's the
size of an escalated ESV what the hell
is this another trunk this is a trunk
yeah so you have a trunk in the front
you have a trunk in the back
oh that's the selling point you have two
trunks yeah so very small boot back here
and then you have this one in the this
was pretty cool so that's a carrying bag
if I'm not mistaken yep gold tool kit
for what like just for anything in
general you know semic Cen so it's bound
to break yeah come on come on in yeah it
feels like you're on a roller coaster it
feels like feels like you're hella black
bro I'm not going to lie this in here is
super cool I literally feel like I'm bro
like this [__] feels hella futuristic so
this is how we are inside here right now
so I'm literally right down the middle
very spacious is like right squeezed
into now that [__] is not spacious
you're like behind the chair and then I
don't know how this is going to go down
welcome so I'm in so I close right here
Yep this is not like the 720 you could
drive with the doors open no if you do
that then you have to get out of the car
put it into neutral and close the doors
physically oh hell no when I take out my
girls BR this is like perfect I'll be
like yo what's
up a Ruby Rose build right here bro you
won't even be able to fit right there
yeah you get some thicker you like a
think though oh boy sorry come here can
you just go to McLaren and get one of
these or no no you cannot no there's 106
examples and they were sold out before
McLaren was done saying the word speed
tail oh yeah oh slippery oh no this [__]
goes this [__]
goes yeah being in the middle it just
makes makes you one of the f
it definitely lives up to the name speed
you I love Mexico yeah we're
Mexico I'm like I'm like 30%
throt
SM and it's making like Pagani noises
yeah
sounds like a Honda cord when they put
an intake on
it smells like peanuts yeah yeah there's
so much going on in here it just smells
like peanuts yeah we're all so close to
each other bro you know four guys
together wait that's all the window goes
down yeah man how much more do you need
oh dude that's [__] nothing this is
like the center all you do is give your
license and registration anyways oh man
that's literally nothing so there's no
rear view mirror nope so how how do I
look back if you don't brother life is
about going forward
progression that's why when you look
back you get stuck start to get contempt
with the moment you really got to keep
going I wish I could grab his
face but I going only grabb the seat
belt all ready traction control off
traction controls off boys ready
can you turn it back on
yeah I want to let you guys out I both
buttons oh up
yeah
hit look cool no and you can choose what
side you want to leave from yeah for
real I can this side and this
side yo I promise you like an old 70y
old guy cannot drive Lea no no no no no
never never
okay I don't I don't really like the
color though I'm not going to lie you
can't see right I can't see nothing such
an old man car yeah it is an old M car
this [__] is
sick that one's dope I mean you know
what's better than a Bugatti right what
two
Bugattis Andre tap could
never Andre tap could never
N speed we already have a Bugatti be
[__] I mean the purple was sick yeah
this is sick wow how much is this [__]
bro how much your Pier SPS like four or
five mil how much is a speed tail how
much is a speed
tail probably 3 mil you take the Bugatti
for a test drive I know how it drives I
have a Bugatti maybe this one maybe
definitely looks hella different this is
more like the Andrew tape Bugatti yeah
this is the Andrew tape Bugatti if this
car would to be this bronze color just
like this this would be exactly andate
spaghetti if it were to be the color
like this what's up with this this [__]
is sick balloon white aventor s Roadster
hell no this red interior
too no bro sick this like it's like 10
years old bro hell no so what what are
you talking about this this is what I'm
talking about bro you just burned your
last one to the ground how does that
even happen well that didn't take too
long bro the Bugatti dude what are you
talking about there's no way on Earth
but but we were we were just so
different there so how how do I look
back you don't brother life is about
going forward progression yeah that's
the thing I don't know I felt a little
sus you know having you know two guys
super close to me yeah but that's just
this would be the only time that ever
happens just have a point there I'm not
going to lie and this you can only fit
one person I mean it's up to you I just
feel like you have a Bugatti
already but you know what he just said
know what's better than woman
Bugatti two
Bugattis we'll take care of it people
probably come here and like yeah bro let
me just test drive this I mean it's
different bro I I already have a Bugatti
you know and like I have credibility
here I could just come here and ask to
drive this car because it's
me and I mean very humbly like I I own a
Bugatti currently I have 15 cars with
these people you know not some random
guy you know I'm Legit this is very cool
very very cool up dude that's nice it's
it's a rental it's a rental yeah oh
where what company uh the guys over
there they're renting them oh they're oh
that's what that place says yeah they
ran cars oh I saw somebody bring it back
earlier I thought you were driving nah
my first time driving yeah bro that's
nice [__] thank it's a ROM I want to hit
it got [__] sound sounds uh sounds
like Perfection wait the people that
made the Bugatti do they have an accent
or no I think the people that made the
Bugatti are French are they French wa we
we
oh I think that's Italian Italian [__]
French I think there you go you got
[Music]
it turn off got scared holy [__] I'll
can terar
everywhere yeah my current Bugatti does
not have anywhere near as much carbon
fiber has this and you want to know
what's crazy this has a bigger Wing like
if you look back the wing is a lot
bigger but I have a lot more visibility
off of this one cuz I guess the other
one is angled a little bit upwards and
I'm not able to see that's
clear Jesus I'm not going to lie I'm
going to scare the streets are wet and
on my Bugatti I don't think it's a good
idea to hit a John
V oh hell no this [__] doesn't [__] hell
no what's more of a flex having two
Bugattis or having a Bugatti and a speed
tail I feel like nobody knows what a
speed tail is I feel like they see that
man has another 570 yeah McLaren they're
probably think it's like a million
dollar no speeds are for sure over $3
million us I mean having two Bugattis I
feel like it's the biggest [__] you ever
people would be like this guy just not
even real it's not real it's not
possible tell you what boys anything is
possible anything that you put your mind
to and you don't ever let anybody get in
the way of your vision is
possible you know what I was about to go
into like a motivational sector but I'm
going to floor real quick
so I was honestly surprised you made it
that far with the motivation without
saying something out of pocket I going
to say some sus ass [__] I said you know
what
Jesus thank you wow you see that you got
to go in to get out the way read this
for 20 minutes yeah we only PID for 20
minutes are you serious yeah we're going
only for 20 minutes yeah how much is 20
$500 huh $50 $50 bucks for 20 minutes
[__] dude what are you guys videoing for
uh YouTuber no we're for the rental
company oh
you're that's sweet all right all right
see you oh W they're giving away pretty
cheap rentals bro every just walk s at a
car this is pretty cool GT3
R I mean bro we already have one yeah we
already have a g your ass you know I was
always against paying half a million
dollars for a Porsche I have always been
against it until I bought my GT3 for A4
million and then I just fell in love
with por and I said you know what I need
an
[Music]
RS I think two Bugattis would be such a
flex it cuz you know why because if you
can't buy something two times
technically can't afford it I wasn't I
mean it's a [__] Bugatti you know
what I'm saying like there's nothing
like a Bugatti so so put your plate on
it
exterminator I don't know bro let's go
do some numbers let's see what you got
bro see this is where the scam comes out
a number I think I left this one C for
price too
yeah so we're now here with my new car
and obviously you know what car it is
cuz you saw the thumbnail of the video
and yes I got my new Bugatti Chiron and
I'm here at Dunkin Donuts right now not
to get a
donut holy sh that's pretty hard yo
probably wondering why I'm here at
Dunkin Donuts and with my new Bugatti
and this is because this is where it all
started about 7 years ago I was working
at a Dunkin' Donuts one just like this
one not this one specifically cuz I'm
really far from the what I used to work
at now fast forward 7 years I'm here in
my second current Bugatti Chiron pure
Sports I've had the car ready for about
3 weeks and I decided to finally do the
video of the car live
it kind of just hits me every once in a
while when I walk into a d Donuts I get
humbled you walk in in the smell gives
me like a reality check of those early
mornings I would pull up at 5:00 600 in
the morning those late nights that I
would leave and I would not want to be
in there working I would want to be out
living my life doing whatever I want how
I am now you know I don't really want to
be like another one of these guys on the
internet that tells you guys you have to
do hard work you have to show up every
single day I feel like all that [__] is
super cliche but it's the [__] truth
there's no other formula to success
other than showing up and giving 100%
every single day you're not going to get
abs you're not going to get strong and
fit if you don't go to the gym and you
don't stay true to your diet you have to
do everything around in order for you to
have those results if one component is
missing it won't work out it's like an
engine of a vehicle you have an engine
of a car that has one hose that's loose
or one piston that's messed up the car
isn't going to run right it's exact same
thing on your journey to success if you
do everything but take big risk or you
do everything but show up every single
day it's not going to work out I did not
get here by half assing this [__] I
doubled down and gave every single piece
of myself stuff that I would every
single day fire it's a rental oh it's
tal I don't know it's not mine oh it's
not yours no I don't know who it is oh
are you a YouTuber no no I do only fans
oh you do only yeah
yeah thanks subscribe you guys should
subscribe to the channel cuz obviously
people believe anything nowadays I I
probably actually believe that it's a
rental but honestly guys I don't want to
sound repetitive and I don't want to be
another person that tells you the same
thing you know what you have to do to be
successful get the [__] up go out there
and go do it does it suck yes is it hard
yes you know what else sucks being stuck
in the same position you know what else
is hard not growing and letting other
people around you Excel while you done
that's even harder to watch but that
being said if you guys don't know who I
am or enjoy these videos and want to see
what other videos we have make sure to
hit that subscribe button and as well as
comments if you guys want to see a full
breakdown of my whole entire car
collection right now which is a little
over $10 million including the Bugatti
Sharon so with that being said enjoy
these next clips of me doing some crazy
[__] in the Bugatti and my other cars
and S and forget boys see you guys in
the next one
[Music]
so you don't believe I worked that dunin
no no no what if I show you a picture
that you okay
okay damn that's crazy how'd you get
here uh bro I do only fans damn you
should get into it bro you do only fans
with the donuts bro and like that [__]
was wild bro yeah oh
[Music]
there was a girl
at she said she cared about
me she tried to make my
[Music]
world the way she thought it should
be yeah we were desperate
there to have each other all love
is a long
[Applause]
long [__] I lowkey did it though yeah
did I lowkey [__] did it bro i' give
you uh 7 out of 10 respectfully and
that's just because we went to Japan if
we never been to Japan that'd be 10 out
of 10 bro facts